http://www.arcadiawaters.com.au/privacy-policy/

1. GENERAL
Welcome to the internet site of Arcadia Group. You can visit the Arcadia Group Internet site without telling us who you are. Particular sections of this Internet site may ask you to send Arcadia Group personal information or messages, including your name, address, phone number and contact email address. You are under no obligation to provide Arcadia Group with these details, except to the extent that you wish to access the services provided by the Arcadia Group internet site. It is our intention in this Privacy Policy to inform you before we collect personal information from you on the Internet. By visiting the Arcadia Group Internet site, you are accepting the practices described in this Privacy Policy.
2. COLLECTION OF INFORMATION
Your personal information is very important to you, and Arcadia Group considers that you should have a right to control the use and disclosure of that information. Information collected by Arcadia Group will only be disclosed in accordance with the terms of this Privacy Policy.
Specifically, at different times, Arcadia Group may collect all or some of the following information from its Internet site:
2.1 Statistical Information
Arcadia Group collects statistical information regarding the use of its Internet site. This collection includes your computer’s Internet Protocol (IP) address and the date and time of your visit. This information is collected to provide Arcadia Group with information about the use of its site and to help it maintain and develop the site to provide better information to users.
2.2 Cookies
Arcadia Group, in order to enhance functionality, may use cookies on its website. The unique user ID contained within a cookie automatically identifies your computer – but not you – to our servers every time you visit our site. Cookies by themselves cannot be used to find out the identity of any user. It involves the collection of information about your computer, including your habits when accessing the Arcadia Group Internet site and any personal information you provide in customising this site. You can prevent this collection of information by disabling your web browser from accepting cookies. This will not prevent you from accessing the Arcadia Group Internet Site; however it may prevent you from utilising all the features in the Arcadia Group Internet Site.
2.3 Requested Personal Information
You may be requested to provide Arcadia Group with personal information including your contact details and e-mail address so that we can send you newsletters, promotional material or further information about Arcadia Group products and services or if you want to have access to specific services for registered Users or Members of the Internet Site. Personal information will only be requested if it is necessary to provide a service to you.
In this instance you should read Arcadia Group Use and Disclosure policy in clause 3.
3. USE AND DISCLOSURE
Arcadia Group will not use or disclose, and will use reasonable endeavours to prevent the use or disclosure of, information provided by a user to Arcadia Group Internet site for a purpose other than the primary purpose of collection (a ‘secondary purpose’), except to the extent:
that the secondary purpose is related to the primary purpose of collection and that you would reasonably expect Arcadia Group to use or disclose the information for the secondary purpose;
that you have consented to the use of the information for the secondary purpose;
that information provided by you, including information relating to transactions, may appear in aggregate form for the purpose of providing statistical information within Arcadia Group or to third parties. This information will not identify you;
necessary in order to enforce any of the terms of an agreement between you and Arcadia Group;
that Arcadia Group has reason to suspect that unlawful activity has been, is being or may be engaged in, and uses or discloses the personal information as a necessary part of its investigation of the matter or in reporting its concerns to relevant persons or authorities;
required or specifically authorised by law; and
provided in co-operation with any governmental authority.
4. ACCESS AND CORRECTION
Where Arcadia Group collects information from you, we will provide you with access to your information at your request except to the extent that:
the request for access is frivolous or vexatious;
providing access would have an unreasonable impact on the privacy of others;
the information relates to existing legal dispute resolution proceedings between you and Arcadia Group,  and the information would not be accessible by the process of discovery in those proceedings; or
providing access would reveal the intentions of Arcadia Group in relation to negotiations with you in such a way as to prejudice those negotiations.
Where information about you is found to be incorrect, incomplete or out of date, Arcadia Group will correct, update, erase or amend the information as appropriate.
5. LINKS FROM THIS SITE
Arcadia Group may link to other Internet sites. It is important that you are aware that any such links are not subject to the same privacy policies and restrictions seen in this Privacy Policy. Please read carefully any policy documents or terms and conditions that appear on linked Internet sites before disclosing any personal information. Arcadia Group is not responsible for any practices on linked Internet sites that might breach your privacy.
6. SECURITY
Arcadia Group acknowledges that security is important. Arcadia Group stores your personal information in secure environments to safeguard it from misuse, disclosure, alteration or destruction. By using the Arcadia Group Internet site you agree that he Internet is inherently insecure. Arcadia Group will use its best endeavours to secure your personal information and cannot provide any definitive assurance regarding security of personal information. By accessing the Arcadia Group Internet Site, you acknowledge that Arcadia Group will not be liable in any way in relation to any breach of security or any unintended loss or disclosure of that information.
7. CHANGES TO PRIVACY POLICY
Arcadia Group may, without notice, amend or modify this Privacy Policy by posting the amended Privacy Policy to the Arcadia Group Internet Site.
8. FEEDBACK, QUESTIONS OR PROBLEMS
Arcadia Group welcomes any feedback you may have regarding our privacy policy. If you have any questions or queries relating to the policy, or if you have any suggestions or problems, please send an email using the email form on the contact page of the Arcadia Group Website.
Arcadia Group
Sales: 1300 88 98 35
Head Office: (08) 9218 8388
E: sales@arcadiagroup.com.au
Request a call backRequest info packRequest a village tour
If  you would like to know more, please fill out the form below and our friendly team will be in touch shortly.
Name*
Email*
Please leave this field empty.
Phone*
Which Village(s) interest you?
SwanbourneBictonMaddingtonMandurahGeraldtonPort Denison
Message
Please leave this field empty.
Please leave this field empty.
Preferred Tour Days
SundayMondayTuesdayWednesdayThursdayFridaySaturday
Which Village(s) interest you?
SwanbourneBictonMaddingtonMandurahGeraldtonPort Denison
How did you hear about Arcadia Waters?
GoogleRadioWord of mouthLocal NewspaperFamiliar with the locationFacebookOther
Request Info Pack
Order an Information Pack
Please complete the details below and we will send you more information
Please leave this field empty.
Which Villages are you interested in?
GeraldtonSwanbourneBictonMaddingtonMandurahPort Denison
How did you hear about Arcadia Waters?
GoogleRadioWord of mouthLocal NewspaperFamiliar with the locationFacebookOther
